Thank you for watching!
You have another one...
I got it at a soooo good time.
Hello?
Good evening.
Uh, just a minute...
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry, I'm a little nervous at home.
I'm sorry.
I have to be quiet at this time of night.
Oh, I see.
That's right.
I'm sure you've heard that before.
I thought you'd understand right away.
Wait a minute.
Oh, so those tears you cried when we said goodbye were fake tears.
Wait a minute... really... this is...
Is this the wrong team for this show, or is it really...
Don't give me that feeling when you don't understand me right away.
Okay, I'll keep my voice up like I always do.
Okay.
Our next guest is here.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's been a while.
Long time no see.
I can't do it.
It's been a long time.
Not at all. I've never called you.
I've never done that.
I've never done that before, and I'm sorry to call you at this hour.
I just finished putting her to bed, and she's talking in the next room next to where the kids are sleeping.
No, no, no, no, it's fine. It's totally fine.
I'm glad. I wouldn't have noticed. I'm not defending myself, but...
I'm not defending myself, but...
I'm not defending myself, but... no, no, no... it's really unlikely that we'll talk on the phone.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I've had people come on the radio before.
Yes! The last time I saw him was on the radio.
Because you're talking right in front of me.
I'm fine.
I'm looking at your Instagram, so I've got all that information.
Thank you very much.
The last time I saw you was less than two years ago.
I was on Hama-san's radio show.
Yes, yes.
Between then and today, you had two children.
No, you didn't. Yes, you did.
Yes, yes, yes.
So I saw it on the news.
I saw that.
Oh.
So, you know...
Just before you became a mom.
Right before I was born.
That's right. That's right, that's right, that's right.
I was born a few days later.
That's right. - That's right.
How are you doing?
Well, you know, I'm still doing the same thing.
What are you doing these days?
Well, recently we had our first tour in two and a half years with a new band member.
It's been two and a half years since I've had a new member in the band, and we've finished it successfully.
I'm also doing a radio talk on a daytime show.
I've also been invited to do some performances.
I don't know if it's the same as when we were working together.
I see you on TV a lot.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But I've done a lot of commercials and MCing.
I've done a lot of things.
No, but yes, I did start doing one of those things.
Do you think I'm selling well?
No, no, I don't think so.
I don't think so.
I just think that people like me have a chance to do something like that.
What? What do you mean, like me?
I mean, you know...
We've been working together for four and a half years.
I mean, you're a TV watcher.
That's why, you know, you'll be on TV.
I mean, it's not that I'm not a TV person, but I think that it takes a lot of great people to speak publicly or do something that's a little too visible, you know... you know...
I'm a band member, and I've been working hard since I was 20 years old, so....
I'm a band member, and I'm not going to make it my main profession and... I've been working hard since I was 20 years old.
So even for someone like that, there are still people who are interested in me,
I am happy to know that people are interested in my work.
The number of opportunities has increased.
Humble as ever.
I like that about you!
What?
I like that! I like that about you!
You've always said that, but you know what?
Humble.
Yes, but...
No, but, you see, that's the thing about working together...
That's really big, really big. Not because we're talking now, but because I've said it everywhere.
Really? I mean, who's watching this? I'm sure there are people who don't know that we were doing a show together... Yes, we were doing a music show, the two of us, folks. There are a lot of cameras in front of me right now.
I'm going to go ahead and tell them that yes, we were doing it together. We worked together for about four and a half years. Four and a half years. Four and a half years is quite a long time, you know.
Yes, it was quite a big event. I think it's been quite a long time.Yeah, a pretty big event. I think it was quite a long time.
It's a strange thing, when I look at the photos and the guest list, I can't remember it at all, even though four and a half years had passed.
I understand. I have the recordings of each event burned into my memory.
Now I have two, on TV. I have been allowed to speak regularly, but not at all back then.
I was allowed to do a little bit of work.
I was allowed to do a little bit now and then.
Oh, really?
You must be lying. You must be lying.
But the Fulcolas team came to talk to me directly,
I thought, "Well, I don't know what Mr. Ekey said or didn't say,
I thought, well, I'll wait until I meet them,
The staff team was really wonderful,
I said, "If it's all right with me," and I said, "Well, it's nice to meet you on the first recording.
Yes, but at that moment, it was already done.
I thought, "This person is easy to work with, I've found someone who is like a great partner.
So, yes, of course, you have a career in the public eye, and you have a lot of experience, physically.
It was a great relief for me to have someone like that say that to me.
If it had been really hard to do, I would have never done it.
I thought I would be fired in a couple of months. That's not true. It was great, right from the beginning.
But it's a strange thing. Looking back on it, I think it has something in common with the distance I feel between myself and my band now,
You were talking after you entered the studio, weren't you? That's right. Maybe we would go backstage and talk backstage.
We don't go back and forth to the dressing rooms and talk.
We didn't know each other's contact information, so in that sense, it was very direct.
That's right. We have a perfect distance between us.
We've been doing it like that for four years.
I don't know a lot of things I don't know at all.
Yes, we do.
Only when we're onstage.
With that kind of tension.
Like the two of us do it together. Yes. That's a bit similar to when the four of us get together, since we don't talk at all behind the scenes.
I'm glad to hear that. I think that a high start is good on TV or at a live performance, but if it doesn't happen, people's impression of Okamoto-ji will be very negative.
If we don't do that, we won't become the Okamotoji that everyone has an impression of. Yes, yes.
And it's amazing, looking back on it, I think it was close.
I understand. I also had the feeling that I was like a partner, though a bit cheeky.
It was like I only had to make the right decision on the day of the performance.
Yes, yes, that's true. So we didn't chat unless there was a break before the next guest arrived.
That's right.
But there was one thing that was bothering me.
To be honest, I don't like people who are very excited.
And sometimes, when a guest comes in with a lot of tension, I feel like I'm a little bit turned off.
Once, just before a very excited guest was about to arrive, Mr. Hammer secretly said to me
But once, just before a very excited guest was about to arrive, Mr. Hammer secretly told me that the person coming from now on would be a little high-spirited.
I had never said I didn't like people with high tension.
I wonder if he sensed that, or if he just said it without thinking about it.
I don't know if this is an answer to your question,
The point is, I'm not saying that I actually had an intuition when you just said that to me,
I don't mean to say that I actually had a hunch, but the fact that you are telling me this is a good thing,
I think he thought it would be easier for him to do it if he told me,
I think he was unconsciously aware of it.
My partner! That's really great!
You know, I don't say that every time. There were days when my acquaintances came, weren't there?
Yes. Someone I've worked with before. But I didn't say to them, "Why are you like this?
I never did, but that one time, I wondered why he said that. And in fact, because I had that information, I was able to do my best.
Oh, I see, but you can do it with that in mind, can't you?
I can do it with that intention, right?
Yes, I am glad I listened to you because you really understood my personality.
I thought, "Well, you know, Hanyu-san really understands my personality.
I think we were unconsciously trying to balance each other's weight.
Yes, there was.
I think it would be better to leave it to them now.
I don't know.
Well, it's the other way around. There were some things.
So idols appeared on the program, band members appeared on the program, and many of the senior members of the company came to the show, right?
Yes, it was. So, we were all kind of standing up to each other in our respective fields of expertise.
I think we were trying to balance each other out. I think it was unconscious.
That's right. It brings back memories. It was fun.
It really was. Just the other day, a woman I have been working with on the radio for about the same amount of time, four or five years, decided to graduate from her regular show.
We were just talking about how she might cry at the end of the show. The staff team and I were just talking about it.
I was talking with the staff team about how I would do my best not to cry during the final episode.
Right before the episode aired, I told everyone that I didn't think I would cry, and they said, "You know, you're always in a mask.
No, no, no, I was talking about the last episode of Daffle Chorus.
But it's already been aired.
But it might be the first and last time, and it's not like I'm in the last year of my career.
Really? I was surprised when Hama-san cried the last time.
I said it was over.
You said you felt triggered when I said I was going to be like that.
I tried not to cry, but...
But you cried?
When I looked at her side, she was like, "You're going to cry? I guess so.
I think everyone on the staff probably felt the same way.
When I answered the phone for the first time today, she cried when we said goodbye, but I told her that's what I meant.
I got through to him right away.
I thought it meant something when I said goodbye.
I was like, "They didn't say who this is, so what am I going to do now? I was like, "Who?
Have you been crying lately?
When do you cry?
Lately, I guess.
Recently?
Like at the movies?
Yes, I've cried at those kinds of things.
But I'm often told that I don't seem to cry a lot.
Not at all. I cry when I see things like the crash-landing of love.
What? That's too strong!
Of course you do.
No way!
I'm sorry, but yes.
It's not like I'm crying a lot.
Hana-san, with her modesty...
She's amazing.
She's straight as a person, but twisted in a good way.He's a straight shooter as a person, but twisted in a good way.
Well, I've been told that.
I've always thought that you and I have the same twisted way of thinking.
That's why I've always thought that I'm the same as you in the way I twist things, like a straight love story.
I'm like, "Oh, no! That's why I always thought she looked at straight love stories like that.
Right? That's my impression.
I think everyone thinks so.
No, I totally get it.
I also feel that I'm a bit emotional about things that go along with music, so that's something that happens.
I see.
So I think it's probably due to my age.
Wait a minute, you're so cute!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Tamahiki-san is cute.
Maybe it wasn't like that when we were working together.
You're aging well.
I wonder if it's a good thing...
I'm sure it's the same for Becky.
Image stops at a certain point, doesn't it?
It's impossible to improve that image, even if you go on TV a lot.
No matter what you do, it's difficult to change the impression that someone has of you, and it's difficult to change it.
Well, the person has already made up his or her mind.
I think there are a lot of people who have stopped at the image of you as a brusque person who doesn't seem to get along with other people.
I see... I see... So, I was working with Mr. Bekki, too, so we had a lot of conversations in the background.
You said earlier that we didn't have a lot of behind-the-scenes conversations, but I'm sure I'm getting information from you that I can't get from that kind of thing.
That's right.
I have a lot of points that are the opposite of the impression people have of Bekki on TV.
But, I don't know if I should say this, but... the core color has changed... well, I don't see him now, but maybe it's because we're filming.
What? Really?
I didn't notice.
It's an excuse to say it now, but...
I have a totally different impression of you.
I see. That's why.
Maybe the phone was a big factor.
Well, you know, there's no camera.
Yeah.
You know, being at home.
Yes, that's part of it.
But, you know...
I'm sure your mother is a big woman.
I just had a hunch.
I wonder...
I don't know.
The tone of her voice is completely different.
But still...
1... you have to say what you want to say so that the audience can catch it.
To make sure the words you want to deliver are caught.
I have to speak softly...
I might be conscious of my tone of voice every day.
I'm really impressed.
"Oh, Becky, you're Becky," and we talked about the old days.
If you don't talk that loud, it's not like you used to talk that loud.
I don't think I used to talk that loud, so now I have the impression of Becky's voice.
But when I compare it with her voice, it's a little different.
Oh, I guess you're right.
Oh, my God, it's a bar-ha!
It's a life-changing event. It's the most life-changing event of your life.
Well, there are some things that men can't measure up to.
But that's what they say about singers, too.
When a singer gives birth, her vocal changes or her color changes.
So she's physically changing, right? Her body is amazing.
That's amazing. He's so sweet. Who did you think he was?
I'm so happy. Finally.
I'm so happy.
I guess it's because I knew her before she became a mother.
It's hard for me to describe my relationship with you in one word, but if you had to give it a title, what would it be? Friends? It's not like we're friends.
Well, we're not friends... not friends at all.
What is it with us? I don't know. I don't like the way things are going.
I don't know. I don't know.
We're not just co-stars.
But we are different in age, but I think it was a turning point for both of us.
I see... Of course, I haven't seen all of your life, so I'm sure there are many turning points.
I think it was one of the turning points for me.
You know...
I shared that time with him, so I don't think I can call him a friend, and of course I feel like I owe him something, but to call him a benefactor is a bit exaggerated.
But people wonder why I've been working with Bekki for four years, don't they?
Yeah, that's why it's difficult, isn't it?
When I look back on it...
I mean, some people say, "What did you fight for?
If you are fighting against your surroundings, your environment, and the things you've done...
If you are fighting against your surroundings, your environment, and what you've done, then that's what it means to you.
I see. It's because of that, isn't it?
I don't know if I can call him a friend, since I don't have his contact information.
But he's younger than me.
You don't know his contact information.
It's an Instagram DM, right?
When it's really important.
It's been a year or something, and then I get a DM.
Can I DM you again once in a while?
It's pretty funny that you're promising that right here and now.
You're having a meeting here to discuss how to DM people on Instagram.
I told him to do it on his own.
It's true.
I'm sure the people watching will think it's a really strange relationship.
That's true.
A lot of people who used to watch the show still say that.
I'm sure there are people like that.
But now, here for the first time...
I'm sure there are a lot of people
I'm sure there are a lot of people out there.
I'm sure they're thinking, "What kind of relationship is this?Surely you must be wondering what kind of relationship this is.
It's strange, isn't it?
That's why I'm a little happy when I see something without my permission.
I don't know what it is.
I know. Whenever I get news, too...
I think, "Congratulations! I think, "Congratulations!
It's a strange feeling... I don't mean it's a strange feeling, but it's like I'm not a stranger to this world.
It's not like I'm a stranger to it.
I also have a program that says, "This is my first year anniversary since I started working here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Each time I think about it, I feel happy that it has lasted a year,
It's amazing that we've been doing it for more than four years.
I am glad to be remembered at such milestones.
In my career, I think the band, radio, and full chorus are the longest. The longest one.
I'm glad to be included. I'm glad.
We are now in our 12th year.
Of course the band has been around for a long time.
We have been doing the radio show since we were about 19 years old, but not the same show.
That's a long time in the sense that it's been a really long time, but in terms of things other than music, the longest time I've made music with the same group of people is only with Fulcora, so that's all I have so far.
Oh, really?
That's right. So everything is a yardstick, really.
Wow. That makes me happy.
I tend to chase afterimages, don't I?
I don't reflect it to other people at all, but I think back to how Mr. Bekki did at that time.
I think that the staff members were really good in that team, too.
Together...
I feel like we really made something together.
I'm glad you remember me.
I didn't know what to think of it, but it was fun.
I'm glad you're here, but...
I'm glad you picked up the phone, but don't you think you'd be nervous if you were doing this?
Yes, I would. Oh, no.
Right?
No, I don't.
I wasn't lying about my tears when I said I'd get it.
I was just trying to make a point.
It's true, though.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no.
But yes, I'm so happy.
I'm so sorry. Thank you very much.
You look refreshed. Thank you very much.
I'm thinking of hanging up now.
Of course. No, no, no. You have kids.
I'm sorry to keep you talking at this hour.
I want to sleep a little longer.
Of course you do. You go to bed early.
Yes, yes, yes. Are you all right?
Thank you very much.
Do you have any, uh, announcements? Are you okay?
No, I'm fine. I'm not fine.
No, I'm fine. Do you have to announce anything?
It's just a phone call. I'm fine.
Are you all right?
Thank you very much. Good luck.
Good luck.
Bye-bye. It was really nice to meet you.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
That's the first time you called me.
That's why I'm so happy.